<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Star Gamer</title>
  <subtitle>Fleet actions in deep space</subtitle>
  <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app"/>
  <updated>2025-04-25T16:10:31.000+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://stargamer.netlify.app/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Star Gamer</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Coming soon</title>
    <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app/coming-soon/"/>
    <updated>2025-04-25T16:10:31.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://stargamer.netlify.app/coming-soon/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is Starship Combat Games, a brand new site by that&#39;s just getting started. Things will be up and running here shortly. Star Gamer will be building a resource for current and popular past starship combat games. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current news will cover new products and releases and we will also curate resources for older games that may not have official support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id=&quot;get-involved&quot;&gt;Get Involved&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for games to cover so if you would like to send us any press releases or just an email with your preferred copy about your game that would be great. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each game has its own section where we post a general introduction to the game and then update it with relevant news. There is a general questionnaire that is useful to categorise the game and provide the information that is often asked for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please email all submissions to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:stargamersite@proton.me&quot; rel=&quot;noreferrer&quot;&gt;stargamersite@proton.me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>FASA Star Trek Starship Combat Simulator Introduction</title>
    <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app/fasa-star-trek-starship-combat-simulator/"/>
    <updated>2025-04-25T16:02:30.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://stargamer.netlify.app/fasa-star-trek-starship-combat-simulator/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The FASA Star Trek Starship Tactical Combat Simulator (&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;STSTCS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;) is a tabletop role-playing game supplement released in the mid-1980s by FASA (Fantasy Amateur Simulations Association), which held the license to produce Star Trek gaming products at that time. Here&#39;s a summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gameplay: This game is designed for players to engage in space combat scenarios within the Star Trek universe. It focuses on tactical combat between starships, with rules for movement, combat, and damage. Players can control various Starfleet vessels or ships from different alien races like the Klingons, Romulans, or the Federation&#39;s own ships.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Components: The game includes several components like ship cards or sheets detailing the stats of different starships, counters or miniatures for representing ships on a game board or map, and dice for resolving combat and other random events. There are also extensive tables for ship movement, weapon ranges, damage, and repair.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rules System: The combat system uses a hexagonal grid for movement and positioning, simulating the three-dimensional aspect of space battles. Players decide their ship&#39;s movements, power allocation to systems (like shields, weapons, and engines), and engage in combat rounds where actions like firing phasers or photon torpedoes are resolved.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scenarios: The game comes with pre-designed scenarios or allows players to create their own, setting up different tactical situations or fleet engagements. Scenarios can range from small skirmishes to large fleet actions, each with specific objectives like protecting a convoy or capturing an enemy ship.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Role-Playing Elements: While primarily tactical, it can be integrated with FASA&#39;s broader Star Trek RPG to include role-playing elements where players might take on roles like captain, tactical officer, or engineer, making strategic decisions beyond just combat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Detail and Complexity: The simulator is known for its detailed rules reflecting the complexities of Star Trek technology and combat scenarios. This includes managing energy distribution, dealing with hull and system damage, and the strategic use of different ship capabilities like cloaking devices or tractor beams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Compatibility: It was meant to be used with the broader Star Trek: The Role-Playing Game by FASA, allowing characters from the RPG to command ships in these tactical scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This game appeals to fans of Star Trek who enjoy the strategic and tactical aspects of starship combat, offering a detailed and somewhat complex system to simulate the feel of battles seen in the Star Trek series and films. However, the game&#39;s depth might require some learning curve for new players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/01/fasa-star-trek-starship-combat_1_7d75103a64bf749571387b0ca6a72336-3411889069-1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;697&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Full Thrust Second Edition Introduction</title>
    <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app/full-thrust/"/>
    <updated>2025-04-25T15:52:12.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://stargamer.netlify.app/full-thrust/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Published in 1990&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full Thrust Second Edition is a tabletop miniature wargame by Ground Zero Games that simulates space combat in a sci-fi setting. Here&#39;s a summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gameplay: Players command fleets of starships, engaging in tactical space battles. The game uses a turn-based system where players manage movement, combat, and ship systems. It&#39;s known for its fast-paced and straightforward mechanics, making it accessible yet tactical.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Components: The game includes ship templates or counters, dice (six-sided), and often custom miniatures or models representing various spacecraft. Players can use any miniatures, but the game provides stats for ships from different factions or designs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rules System: &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Movement: Ships move with pre-plotted free-form movement, with thrust managed by &quot;thrust points&quot; representing engine power. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Combat: Weapons like lasers, missiles, and particle beams have different ranges and effects. Combat resolution involves dice rolls, typically comparing the attack roll against a target number based on range, weapon, and defensive capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damage: Ships have areas or systems (like engines, weapons, shields) that can be damaged or destroyed, affecting performance. Damage allocation can be random or determined by player choice for strategic depth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ship Design: One of the hallmarks of Full Thrust is its ship design system. Players can design their own ships using a points system, balancing speed, armor, firepower, and other attributes like ECM (Electronic Counter Measures) or fighters.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scenarios and Campaigns: While the core game provides scenarios for immediate play, it&#39;s flexible for players to create their own or engage in campaigns where fleet composition and ship status persist between games, adding a strategic layer to fleet management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Setting: The game doesn&#39;t enforce a specific universe, allowing for generic sci-fi or adaptation to existing franchises or custom settings. However, it has its own background with factions like the NAC (New Anglian Confederation) or the ESU (Earth Systems Union).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Editions: The Second Edition refined the rules from the first, improving clarity, balancing, and adding options. Subsequent expansions and rule clarifications have been published, but the Second Edition remains a popular choice for its balance of simplicity and depth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community: Full Thrust has a dedicated following, with fans often creating additional rules, ships, and scenarios. There&#39;s a significant amount of homebrew content available, expanding the game&#39;s scope and replayability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full Thrust is celebrated for its blend of accessibility and tactical gameplay, making it a go-to for both new gamers interested in space combat and veterans looking for a system with depth in fleet engagements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/01/FT2cover-1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;kg-image&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; width=&quot;180&quot; height=&quot;250&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>New FASA Carrier Models</title>
    <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app/new-fasa-carrier-models/"/>
    <updated>2025-04-25T17:07:24.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://stargamer.netlify.app/new-fasa-carrier-models/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-bookmark-card&quot;&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;kg-bookmark-container&quot; href=&quot;https://cults3d.com/en/3d-model/game/tmp-era-fanon-carriers-star-trek-starship-parts-kit-expansion&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-bookmark-content&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-bookmark-title&quot;&gt;TMP era fanon carriers - Star Trek starship parts kit expansion&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-bookmark-description&quot;&gt;[This kit can also be found on my Google Drive mirror (https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1_Vh-D_-8QJXlsq9R7h16Xty0Efo_GFzi?usp=drive_link). ]
Note: I’ve created a Patreon to support my modelling projects. If you’ve found my work useful, have the means, and would like to support my efforts, please give it a look (https://www.patreon.com/CaptainMojoShipyards). I will continue to release my designs for free on Cults 3D and Thingiverse, but Patreon members will get early access and in progress updates on my new projects, and it will serve as a central location for announcements. Thanks for reading!
This is a follow-up on my last kit, which covered TOS era Federation carriers. In this kit we move forward a few decades to The Motion Picture era.
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/d6406de3-40de-48ff-ab3a-994241b68670/__preview.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/d6406de3-40de-48ff-ab3a-994241b68670/__preview.png)
As noted in the previous kit, there’s zero on-screen canonical evidence of fighters or carriers pre-Dominion war (aside from the quasi-canonical Star Fleet Battles designs, which I do not cover). In this kit, I’ve pulled from Fanon designs found at the web site shipschematics.net (http://www.shipschematics.net/startrek/federation_data.php?filter=Carrier), as well as ships of my own devising.
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/a3ceab48-c33c-482c-bdfa-c9bc34a4f131/__preview2.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/a3ceab48-c33c-482c-bdfa-c9bc34a4f131/__preview2.png)
The contents of this kit are provided into four zip files:
fed-carriers-TMP-ship-stls.zip – Print-ready combined ship STL files.
fed-carriers-TMP-blender-parts-files.zip – Blender files with parts files pre-arranged as they are on the output ship stl files.
fed-carriers-TMP-blender-source-files.zip – The Blender source files used to generate the part STL files.
fed-carriers-TMP-parts-stls.zip – Individual STL part files for digital kitbashing.
This kit supports the following variant ship classes:
Ark Royal class fleet carrier (AKA Ranger)
This design was first seen in the game Starfleet Command II - Empires at War (https://memory-alpha.fandom.com/wiki/Star_Trek:_Starfleet_Command_II_-_Empires_at_War), released by Taldren/Interplay in the year 2000. Originally known as the Ranger class, the design has recently been seen again in Star Trek Online, where it’s known as the Ark Royal class (Ark Royal being the default ship name in the original game). My version attempts to match the original game art where possible, differing most noticeably from what you’ll see in STO with a slightly hexagonal lower hull. Note this ship is much larger than the other ships in this kit, rivaling the Ambassador and even approaching the Galaxy class in size.
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/c70a80f5-1dc1-4ed2-8efd-918f13560844/_preview-ark-royal.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/c70a80f5-1dc1-4ed2-8efd-918f13560844/_preview-ark-royal.png)
Ariel class shuttle carrier
Taking some design cues from the (in)famous Ralph McQuarrie redesign of the Enterprise for the canceled Planet of The Titans (https://forgottentrek.com/phase-2/planet-of-the-titans-the-film-that-wasnt/) movie project but using the more familiar refit Constitution style components, the Ariel originates from the fan work “Heavy Cruiser Evolution Blueprints (https://www.cygnus-x1.net/links/lcars/enterprise-evolution.php)” by David Nielsen and Aridas Sofia. I’ve also a three-nacelle version of this ship in the kit. Ariel is another very large ship.
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/da723f21-3443-44c1-a84d-da1a3686543d/_preview-ariel.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/da723f21-3443-44c1-a84d-da1a3686543d/_preview-ariel.png)
Coronado class thru-deck carrier (Forrestal subtype)
The originally TOS version by the team at Starstation Aurora. This TMP style model is inspired by the refit Forrestal subtype designed by Anthony “Kelvin0514” Auverdin (http://www.shipschematics.net/startrek/related_ships.php?search_source=Internet+-+Anthony+%22Kelvin0514%22+Auverdin%2C+inspired+by+Todd+Guenther%27s+%26+Eric+Kristiansen%27s+works).
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/7277cd5a-f5e6-47c2-b7ec-cd705d9d93c5/_preview-coronado.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/7277cd5a-f5e6-47c2-b7ec-cd705d9d93c5/_preview-coronado.png)
Dakota class heavy shuttle carrier
Design by Eric Kristiansen (Jackill) (https://www.cygnus-x1.net/links/lcars/JAC.php). A stretched double Miranda hull, with many, many shuttle bays. In addition to the three nacelle version based on source art, I’ve added added a 4-nacelle version I’m calling the MK-2media/a6ddb10e1850eca524f4d739d489c7c1.png
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/4d559e0e-d439-4f39-9dc1-7c60e0c50187/_preview-dakota-mk1.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/4d559e0e-d439-4f39-9dc1-7c60e0c50187/_preview-dakota-mk1.png)
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/86196609-d5f4-4197-b65f-b20a34963fef/_preview-dakota-mk2.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/86196609-d5f4-4197-b65f-b20a34963fef/_preview-dakota-mk2.png)
Drake class thru-deck carrier
TOS version by David Tiekamp. TMP refit is my own interpretation.
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/3d9b4c41-4c84-4c88-9537-82b812dcd16c/_preview-drake.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/3d9b4c41-4c84-4c88-9537-82b812dcd16c/_preview-drake.png)
Franz Joseph Federation class dreadnought
My interpretation of a thru-deck carrier conversion of the Federation class.
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/93e207ce-343f-4bb0-9766-dd5a69ca2796/_preview-federation-dnv.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/93e207ce-343f-4bb0-9766-dd5a69ca2796/_preview-federation-dnv.png)
Long Island class carrier
As with the TOS version, the refit Long Island is based on the original art of Neal “Vance” Davidson / Federation Frontiers
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/32748b10-c0d3-4e24-bcf3-21d03f0b71ff/_preview-long-island.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/32748b10-c0d3-4e24-bcf3-21d03f0b71ff/_preview-long-island.png)
Minas Gerais class light carrier
My own design, the Minas Gerais uses a double rear-hull inspired by the Dakota, but not stretched, resulting in a standard Miranda class length.
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/5aeadd50-ff2c-4394-b97e-8a88370929b9/_preview-minas-gerais.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/5aeadd50-ff2c-4394-b97e-8a88370929b9/_preview-minas-gerais.png)
Oriskany class thru-deck carrier
Design by Eric Kristiansen (Jackill).
https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/54a28fe2-4611-4c4c-b687-2ea04ace62af/_preview-oriskany.png (https://fbi.cults3d.com/uploaders/22710918/illustration-file/54a28fe2-4611-4c4c-b687-2ea04ace62af/_preview-oriskany.png)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-bookmark-metadata&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;kg-bookmark-icon&quot; src=&quot;/content/images/icon/cults-bce86dad0556a167574b04b1779f0ed89b6c39b9b1e7e5c91bd73067ab121d0a.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kg-bookmark-author&quot;&gt;Cults 3D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-bookmark-thumbnail&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/thumbnail/__preview.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; onerror=&quot;this.style.display = &#39;none&#39;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Captain Mojo has released new carrier models for Star Trek games.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a follow-up on my last kit, which covered TOS era Federation carriers. In this kit we move forward a few decades to The Motion Picture era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As noted in the previous kit, there’s zero on-screen canonical evidence of fighters or carriers pre-Dominion war (aside from the quasi-canonical Star Fleet Battles designs, which I do not cover). In this kit, I’ve pulled from Fanon designs found at the web site shipschematics.net, as well as ships of my own devising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>FASA STSTCS Gallery</title>
    <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app/gallery/"/>
    <updated>2025-04-25T15:59:50.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://stargamer.netlify.app/gallery/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-container&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-row&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2024/05/Art-1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;736&quot; height=&quot;552&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2024/05/Art-1.jpeg 600w, /content/images/2024/05/Art-1.jpeg 736w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2024/05/feature-starttrekpart3.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;376&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2024/05/feature-starttrekpart3.jpg 600w, /content/images/size/w1000/2024/05/feature-starttrekpart3.jpg 1000w, /content/images/2024/05/feature-starttrekpart3.jpg 1200w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2024/05/Star_Trek_II_The_Wrath_of_Khan_020-960421766.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1024&quot; height=&quot;438&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2024/05/Star_Trek_II_The_Wrath_of_Khan_020-960421766.jpg 600w, /content/images/size/w1000/2024/05/Star_Trek_II_The_Wrath_of_Khan_020-960421766.jpg 1000w, /content/images/2024/05/Star_Trek_II_The_Wrath_of_Khan_020-960421766.jpg 1024w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-row&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2024/05/GM4UR7WXwAErYxQ.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;2000&quot; height=&quot;1301&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2024/05/GM4UR7WXwAErYxQ.jpeg 600w, /content/images/size/w1000/2024/05/GM4UR7WXwAErYxQ.jpeg 1000w, /content/images/size/w1600/2024/05/GM4UR7WXwAErYxQ.jpeg 1600w, /content/images/size/w2400/2024/05/GM4UR7WXwAErYxQ.jpeg 2400w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/01/GMvcmTPX0AAsbxf.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;275&quot; height=&quot;376&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/01/GMsEnQ8WsAEpEiN.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;2000&quot; height=&quot;1351&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2025/01/GMsEnQ8WsAEpEiN.jpeg 600w, /content/images/size/w1000/2025/01/GMsEnQ8WsAEpEiN.jpeg 1000w, /content/images/size/w1600/2025/01/GMsEnQ8WsAEpEiN.jpeg 1600w, /content/images/2025/01/GMsEnQ8WsAEpEiN.jpeg 2048w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-row&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/01/GM4UXMeWMAAL8Tn.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;2000&quot; height=&quot;1341&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2025/01/GM4UXMeWMAAL8Tn.jpeg 600w, /content/images/size/w1000/2025/01/GM4UXMeWMAAL8Tn.jpeg 1000w, /content/images/size/w1600/2025/01/GM4UXMeWMAAL8Tn.jpeg 1600w, /content/images/size/w2400/2025/01/GM4UXMeWMAAL8Tn.jpeg 2400w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/01/GMsEnX6XwAAg5EB.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;2000&quot; height=&quot;1347&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2025/01/GMsEnX6XwAAg5EB.jpeg 600w, /content/images/size/w1000/2025/01/GMsEnX6XwAAg5EB.jpeg 1000w, /content/images/size/w1600/2025/01/GMsEnX6XwAAg5EB.jpeg 1600w, /content/images/2025/01/GMsEnX6XwAAg5EB.jpeg 2048w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/01/star-trek-ii-the-wrath-of-khan-5a31adeb9a31d.png&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;310&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; srcset=&quot;/content/images/size/w600/2025/01/star-trek-ii-the-wrath-of-khan-5a31adeb9a31d.png 600w, /content/images/2025/01/star-trek-ii-the-wrath-of-khan-5a31adeb9a31d.png 800w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 720px) 720px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;white-space: pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;FASA STSTCS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Full Thrust Gallery</title>
    <link href="http://stargamer.netlify.app/full-thrust-new-releases/"/>
    <updated>2025-04-25T16:01:00.000+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://stargamer.netlify.app/full-thrust-new-releases/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;figure class=&quot;kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-container&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-row&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT140NACnewBBt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;104&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT154-155-134ANACnewT.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;79&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT147NACnewCVBt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;113&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-row&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT146NACnewLSOt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;87&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT145NACnewCVEt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;76&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT144NACnewCVHt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;85&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-row&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT143NACnewCVLt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;85&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT142NACnewSDNt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;106&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;kg-gallery-image&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/content/images/2025/03/FT141NACnewBDNt.jpg&quot; width=&quot;135&quot; height=&quot;97&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;white-space: pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Full Thrust Gameplay&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
